sheezyart.com 2006-12-24

# SA . Privacy Policy

PRIVACY POLICY

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Here at SheezyArt.com, we want you to feel secure when visiting our website. We make sure that everyone on our Cast is committed to protecting your privacy, SheezyArt.com safeguards your personal information to maintain the trust that you hold in us. SheezyArt.com makes sure to respect the privacy of visitors to our website by disclosing and explaining in this Privacy Policy how we collect, use and share information about you from us and the choices that you can make about the way your information is collected, used and shared. We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy and those of all web sites you visit.   
This Privacy Policy applies to all services and sub-sites available under the domain SheezyArt.com. Although this is a global privacy policy, each regional or country site may have rules and regulations that are not covered by this policy. We encourage you to read your regional or country level privacy policy before using the site. By visiting this web site, you are agreeing to the terms of this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to periodically revise the terms of this Privacy Policy by updating this page. However, we will not fundamentally alter the scope of the Privacy Policy without your consent. You agree to be bound by subsequent revisions to this Submission Agreement fourteen (14) days after the posting of the revisions to this submission agreement, and notice of the revision posted within a SheezyArt.com Newspost. Accordingly, you should periodically visit this Privacy Policy and the SheezyArt.com Newsposts to review the current terms.

At SheezyArt.com, we collect Personally Identifiable Information and Non-Personally Identifiable Information. Personally Identifiable Information is information that identifies you as an individual, such as your name, email address, age range, etc. It is only obtained when you voluntarily provide the information to SheezyArt.com. Non-Personally Identifiable Information is information that does not identify you as an individual, such as your browser type, IP Address, the URL of the previous web site you visited, etc. We may automatically collect certain types of this information from you when using Sheezyart.com. We may also collect the information that you voluntarily provide, such as information included in response to a questionnaire or survey.

We may use cookie technology to improve your experience on our website and gather data for statistical reporting. A cookie is a small piece of information sent by a web site that is saved by your browser. It holds information a site may need to personalize your experience and gathers web site statistical data. However, none of this information is associated with you as an individual and is measured only in aggregate form. SheezyArt.com may collect IP addresses for the purposes of systems administration, server problem diagnosis and compiling aggregate information. An IP address is a number that is assigned to your computer automatically when you use the Internet. When you visit a particular web page on SheezyArt.com, our servers log your IP address.

SheezyArt.com will never share your information with any third party without your consent, unless we believe such action is required to protect others, conform to applicable law, investigate/prevent illegal activity, or protect or defend the legal rights of SheezyArt.com, or our visitors.

SheezyArt.com is not intended for use by children under the age of 13, nor do we knowingly collect information from such visitors. If we learn that personal information on a child under the age of 13 is collected, we will delete that information from our systems. We encourage parents and guardians to be familiar with the web sites that their children visit.

No data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100 percent secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk.

Our primary purpose in collecting your information on SheeyArt.com is to provide you with a safe and efficient experience and to provide you with services and features that better meet your needs or requests. We only collect information that we consider necessary for achieving this purpose. This is our promise.
